在上一课中，我们讨论了monadic图像处理，这就是我们所采用的
In the last lecture we talked about monadic image processing, and that is where we take
输入图像中的一个像素，对其应用一个函数并将结果放入相应的图像中
a pixel from the input image, apply a function to it and put the result into the corresponding
输出图像中的像素。
pixel in the output image.
我们研究了许多函数：我们研究了伽玛编码和解码;我们
And we looked at a number of functions: we looked at gamma encoding and decoding; we
看着阈值;等等。
looked at thresholding; and so on.
因此，相同的功能应用于图像中的每个像素。
So the same function is applied to every single pixel in the image.
这里发生的是每个输出像素是方形区域中像素的函数
What happens here is that every output pixel is a function of the pixels in a square region
围绕输入图像中的对应点。
around the corresponding point in the input image.
因此函数的输入是多个像素，输出是单个像素值。
So the input to the function is a number of pixels, the output is a single pixel value.
这样一个基于许多像素的函数可以说出一些关于的东西
Such a function, which is based on a number of pixels, can then say something either about
输入方形区域上的像素的均匀性或变化。
the uniformity or the variation of the pixels over that input square region.
我们称之为窗口，用符号W表示。
We call this a window and denote it by the symbol W.
因此，让我们考虑一下我们可能会使用的示例函数，并考虑一个常见的函数
So let’s consider an example function we might use and a common one would be to consider
平均值。
the average.
那么我们要做的就是该方形输入窗口，取所有像素值，
So what we are going to do is for that square input window, take all of the pixel values,
计算平均值，并将平均值放入输出中的相应像素
compute the average, and place the average into the corresponding pixel in the output
图片。
image.
所以这是原始图像，我们以前见过的蒙娜丽莎图像。
So here is the original image, the Mona Lisa image that we have seen before.
输出是7乘7窗口的平均像素值。
And the output is the average pixel value over a 7 by 7 window.
所以平均值可以做的是它可以减少噪音，但我们也看到它减少了噪音
So what the average can do is it can reduce noise but we also see that it reduces the
分辨率-它使这个图像看起来有点模糊。
resolution—it has made this image look somewhat blurry.
让我们看看这在实践中是如何运作的;我在这里构建了一个玩具示例
Let’s see how this actually works in practice; and I have constructed a toy example here
我们在那里输入灰度图像双精度输入图像。
where we have an input grey scale image double precision input image.
因此像素值在0和1之间变化。
So the pixel values vary between 0 and 1.
所以我们有一个灰色的背景，其值为0.3，中间有一个明亮的正方形
So we have a grey background with values of 0.3 and a bright square in the middle where
像素值为0.8。
the pixel values are 0.8.
我们将启动动画，我们在这里看到的是输入像素窗口，它
We will start the animation and what we can see here is the input pixel window, which
在这里显示为红色并且它正在移动，从左到右，从上到下穿过图像。
is shown here as red and it is moving, marching across the image left to right, top to bottom.
你可以在右侧看到的是存入的平均值
And what you can see on the right-hand side are the average values being deposited into
输出图像。
the output image.
需要注意的事项：首先，请注意我们无法计算像素值
Couple of things to note: first of all, note that we can’t compute the pixel values in
最外面的行和列像素。
the outer most row and column pixels.
我们很快就会讨论这个问题。
And we will talk about that shortly.
另请注意，输入图像中明显明亮的亮白色方块已被涂抹
Also note that the quite clearly obvious bright white square in the input image has been smeared
出。
out.
该值仅为0.8，现在仅存在于输出图像中的单个像素处。
That value of 0.8 only exists now at a single pixel in the output image.
在那周围是一些稍微明亮的价值，除此之外是背景，所以我们
Around that are some slightly brighter values and beyond that is the background and so we
看看我们在拍摄蒙娜丽莎图像的平均值时所看到的-尖锐，清脆，
see here what we saw when we took the average of the Mona Lisa image—that the sharp, crisp,
图像中的边界已被涂抹或模糊。
boundaries in the image have been smeared out or blurred.
现在窗口大小的效果产生了真正的不同。
Now the effect of the window size makes a real difference.
再次，这是我们的输入图像，如果我们用7乘7的窗口移动计算平均值
So again, here is our input image and if we compute the average with a 7 by 7 window moving
在输入图像上，这是结果，如果我们增加窗口的大小，
over the input image, this is the result, and if we increase the size of the window,
现在它是一个21乘21的窗口。
now it is a 21 by 21 window.
我们可以看到它确实非常模糊。
We can see that it is very blurry indeed.
因此，往往会发生图像中任何小于大小的特征
So what tends to happen is that any feature in the image that is smaller than the size
窗户的衰减非常强烈。
of the window will be very strongly attenuated.
它将倾向于在输出图像中消失。
It will tend to disappear in the output image.
我们可能会说输出图像模糊，模糊，分辨率较低等等。
We might say that the output image is blurry, fuzzy, has a lower resolution or whatever.
我们已经模糊了，平滑了图像中的细节。
We have blurred out, smoothed over fine detail in the image.
让我们在全尺寸图像中尝试这个。
Let’s try this in a full scale image.
我们将把我们最喜欢的MonaLisa图像加载到工作区变量im中。
We are going to load our favourite image the Mona Lisa into the workspace variable im.
我将使用工作区变量计算一个新图像，我将调用s7。
I am going to compute a new image with the workspace variable I am going to call s7.
并且每个输出像素是像素的7乘7邻域或窗口的平均值
And every output pixel is the average of a 7 by 7 neighbourhood or window of the pixels
在输入图像中。
in the input image.
要做到这一点，我将使用工具箱功能图标，并将解释这一点
To do that I am going to use the tool box function icon and will explain about this
随着我们的进展，功能会更多。
function a bit more as we proceed.
第一个参数是我要执行平均值的图像
The first argument is the image that I am going to perform the average on which is the
蒙娜丽莎图像在工作区变量im。
Mona Lisa image in the workspace variable im.
第二个参数定义了我们计算平均值的区域。
The second argument defines the area over which we compute the average.
现在我想计算7乘7窗口的平均值，所以为了指定，我通过了
Now I wanted to compute the average over a 7 by 7 window and so to specify that, I pass
在具有函数1的矩阵中（7,7）。
in a matrix with a function ones(7,7).
这产生了一个7乘7的矩阵和该矩阵中的每个元素
That produces a matrix that is 7 by 7 and every element in that matrix
是1。
is 1.
所以第二个参数定义了我将要执行平均值的区域
So that second argument defines the region over which I am going to perform the average
对于每个输入像素。
for every single input pixel.
我将展示原始的蒙娜丽莎图像。
I am going to display the original Mona Lisa image.
而我将创造另一个人物。
And I am going to create another figure.
我将展示它的平均版本，我们可以看到有很多
I am going to display the averaged version of that and we can see that there is a lot
背景细节较少。
less detail in the background.
它更顺畅;你可能会说它比较模糊，你可能会说它的分辨率较低。
It is much smoother; you might say it is blurrier, you might say it has got lower resolution.
现在让我们增加我们进行平均的区域的大小。
Now let’s increase the size of the region over which we are doing the averaging.
所以我现在要关联一个21x21像素大小的窗口。
So I am going now to correlate with a window which is 21 by 21 pixels in size.
现在我将显示该图像，我们可以看到这看起来非常模糊。
Now I am going to display that image and we can see that this looks very blurry indeed.
平均像素区域的效果是消除像素区域内的非常精细的细节
The effect of averaging over a region of pixels is to eliminate very fine detail within the
图像，所以任何细节的大小都小于我们使用的窗口，
image, so any detail that is of a size that is smaller than the window that we are using,
在最后一种情况下，21乘21像素，任何大小为1或2像素的细节
in this last case, 21 by 21 pixels, any detail that is the order of 1 or 2 pixels in size
将被淘汰。
is going to be eliminated.